Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Labor Movement Serials WAG.345
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Labor unions and organizations, 1890-2012; 72.1 Linear Feet in 19 record cartons, 29 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript boxes, and 152 flat boxes
  - Subseries I.I: Labor Coalitions and Organizations, 1890-2012; 19.8 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 16 manuscript boxes, and 38 flat boxes
    - Coordinator: Inter-union Coordinating Committee, New York, NY, 1944; cuid10612 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Team Report: J.P. Stevens workers, 1980; cuid10613 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - JLC Monthly News and Activity Review: Jewish Labor Committee, Boston, MA, 1963; cuid10614 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - New Challenges New Directions: Jewish Labor Committee, New York, NY, 2003; cuid10615 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Stronger Together! Building Coalitions: Jewish Labor Committee, New York, NY, 2002; cuid10616 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Honoring Fair Employment Practices Pioneers: 64th Annual Recognition Awards Brunch: Jewish Labor Committee - California/Western Region, Beverly Hills, CA, 1999; cuid10617 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Report: Jewish Labor Committee - N.Y. Workmen's Circle Division, New York, NY, 1943; cuid10618 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - J.L.C. Bulletin: Jewish Labor Committee of Chicago, Chicago, IL, 1952; cuid10619 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Jobs with Justice: Jobs with Justice, Washington, DC, circa 1980s; cuid10620 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - PSL: L. T. Patterson, Cincinnati, OH, 1982; cuid10621 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - L.A. Workers' Voice: L.A. Workers' Voice, Los Angeles, CA, 1994; cuid10622 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Picket Line: L.A.-Student-Worker Action Committee, Los Angeles, CA, 1971-1973; cuid10623 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Conference Report: Labor Action Coalition of New York, Ithaca, NY, 1979; cuid10624 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Labor Action: Labor Action Committee, 1954-1955, 1957, 1970-1973; cuid10625 (Box 151, Folder 6, Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Overtime: Labor Commission of the New America Movement, Chicago, IL, 1982; cuid10626 (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Solidarity: Labor Committee of NY Students for a Democratic Society, New York, NY, 1969; cuid10627 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Hoe Hana: Labor Community Alliance, Honolulu, HI, 1974-1975; cuid10628 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - New Jersey Labor Herald: Labor Herald Publishing Co., Newark, NJ, 1973-1975; cuid10629 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Labor Heritage Foundation News: Labor Heritage Foundation, Washington, DC, 1994-1995; cuid10630 (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - Labor and the Humanities: Labor Institute for Human Enrichment, Inc./National Endowment for the Humanities, Washington, DC, 1981; cuid10631 (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - Relay: Labor Institute of Public Affairs (AFL-CIO), Washington, DC, 1986; cuid10632 (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - Union Yes: Labor Institute of Public Affairs (AFL-CIO), 1993-1995; cuid10633 (Box 142, Folder 17)
    - Labor News: Labor News, Eureka, CA, 1905; cuid10634 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Labor News: Labor News, Worcester, MA, 1962; cuid10635 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Montana Labor News: Labor News, Butte, MT, 1947; cuid10636 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - State Bulletin: Labor Non-Partisan League of New Jersey, Passaic, NJ / Trenton, NJ, 1938; cuid10637 (Box 142, Folder 18)
    - LODF Newsletter: Labor Organizers Defense Fund, New York, NY, 1975; cuid10638 (Box 142, Folder 19)
    - Labor Pains Newsletter: Labor Pains, Cambridge, MA, 1973; cuid10639 (Box 142, Folder 20)
    - Labor Party Press: Labor Party, Washington, DC, 1996-2002; cuid10640 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Worker/El Trabajador: Labor Party League, Montclair, CA, 1975; cuid10641 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - LPON Newsletter: Labor Party Organizing Network, San Francisco, CA, 1993; cuid10642 (Box 142, Folder 21)
    - Newsletter: Labor Press Associates, Washington, DC, 1945; cuid10643 (Box 143, Folder 27)
    - Labor Reporter: Labor Press Unit, New York, NY, 1934; cuid10644 (Box 142, Folder 22)
    - Labor News for Working Families: Labor Project for Working Families, San Francisco, CA, 1994-1997; cuid10645 (Box 142, Folder 23)
    - Bulletin Labor Series: labor publications, New York, NY, 1972-1973; cuid10646 (Box 142, Folder 24)
    - Labor Publications Catalog: Labor Publications/Workers League, New York, NY, 1971; cuid10647 (Box 142, Folder 25)
    - Oklahoma Labor: Labor Publishing Co., Inc., Oklahoma City, OK, 1936; cuid10648 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania Labor Record: Labor Record, Inc., Philadelphia, Pa, 1943-1944; cuid10649 (Box 152, Folder 5-6, Box 38, Folder 3)
    - LRRC Labor Update: Labor Relations and Research Center, University of Massachusetts, Amherst, Amherst, MA, 1991; cuid10650 (Box 142, Folder 26)
    - Southern Labor in Wartime: Labor Research Association/International Publishers Co., Inc., 1942; cuid10651 (Box 142, Folder 27)
    - Labor Today: The Rank and File in Action: Labor Today Associates, Chicago, IL, 1973-1978; cuid10652 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Labor Vets Bulletin: Labor Veterans Group in AVC, Pittsburgh, PA, 1949; cuid10653 (Box 142, Folder 28)
    - Fact Against Fiction: Laborers' International Union of North America, Washington, DC, 1980; cuid10654 (Box 142, Folder 30)
    - Laborers' Benefits Review: Laborers' International Union of North America, Washington, DC, 1988; cuid10655 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Labor's Non-Partisan League National Bulletin: Labor's Non-Partisan League, Washington, DC, 1939; cuid10656 (Box 142, Folder 29)
    - Forward March of American Labor: League for Industrial Democracy, New York, NY, 1953; cuid10657 (Box 142, Folder 31)
    - League for Industrial Democracy News Bulletin: League for Industrial Democracy, New York, NY, 1942; cuid10658 (Box 142, Folder 32)
    - Local 721 Newsletter: Local 721, New York, NY, 1996-1999; cuid10659 (Box 142, Folder 33)
    - Local 966 Union News: Local 966, New York, NY, 1989; cuid10660 (Box 142, Folder 34)
    - Louisiana Labor/Neighbor Journal: Louisiana Labor and Neighbor Alliance, Baton Rouge, LA, 1991; cuid10661 (Box 142, Folder 35)
    - Mass. Rank & File: Mass. Rank & File, Northampton, MA, 1979; cuid10662 (Box 142, Folder 36)
    - Labor Press: Milwaukee County Labor Council (AFL-CIO), Milwaukee, WI, 1995; cuid10663 (Box 142, Folder 37)
    - Coal Field Defender: Miners News Service, Sharon, WV, 1979, 1981; cuid10664 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Minipress: Minifleet Association, Inc., New York, NY, 1984; cuid10665 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Viewpoints MSLC: Missouri State Labor Council, Jefferson City, MO, 1986 (Box 180, Folder 24)
    - National Spotlight: Montgomery-Ward Organizing Committee, New York, NY, 1945; cuid10666 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Fun, Games, Money: Movement Labor New England Free Press, circa 1970s; cuid10667 (Box 142, Folder 38)
    - Spark = La Chispa: N.Y.-N.J. United Workers Organization Electrical Committee, New York, NY, 1976-1977; cuid10668 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Bakery Workers Organize!: N.Y.-N.J. United Workers Organization Food Industry Committee, New York, NY, 1977; cuid10669 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Breaking Through/Workers Unite!: N.Y.-N.J. United Workers Organization Office Committee, New York, NY, 1976-1977; cuid10670 (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Office Workers United: N.Y.-N.J. United Workers Organization Office Committee, New York, NY, 1974-1976; cuid10671 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Full Employment: Proceedings of the Conference on Full Employment CIO Political Action Committee: National Action Committee of the CIO, New York, NY, 1944; cuid10672 (Box 172, Folder 25)
    - NAAO Bulletin: National Association of Artists' Organizations, Washington, DC, 1988; cuid10673 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - New Solidarity Extra: National Caucus of Labor Committees, New York, NY, 1970-1974 (Box 211, Folder 6, Box 213, Folder 17, Box 220, Folder 15)
    - Histadru Foto News: National Committee for Labor Israel, Inc., New York, NY, 1967-1976; cuid10674 (Box 142, Folder 39)
    - Household Employment News: National Committee on Household Employment, Washington, DC, 1979; cuid10675 (Box 142, Folder 40)
    - FEPC Reference Manual: National Community Relations Advisory Council - Committee on Employment Discrimination, New York, NY, 1948; cuid10676 (Box 142, Folder 41)
    - Liguorian: National Council for Industrial Peace, Washington, DC, 1960; cuid10677 (Box 142, Folder 42)
    - Good Jobs for All: National Jobs for All Coalition, New York, NY, 2002; cuid10678 (Box 142, Folder 43)
    - Labor Campaign for Jailed Salvadoran Unionists: National Labor Committee in support of Democracy and Human Rights in El Salvador, New York, NY, 1984; cuid10679 (Box 142, Folder 44)
    - Newsletter: National Labor's Heritage Society, Silver Spring, MD, 1993; cuid10680 (Box 142, Folder 45)
    - Sweatshop Nation: National Mobilization Against Sweatshops (NMASS), New York, NY, 2000; cuid10681 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Your job or your Life?: National Mobilization Against Sweatshops (NMASS), New York, NY, 1997; cuid10682 (Box 142, Folder 46)
    - Unioncraft: National Organization of Industrial Trade Unions, New York, NY, 1970; cuid10683 (Box 142, Folder 47)
    - National Organized Labor Journal: National Organized Labor Journal, New York, NY, 2000 (Box 220, Folder 13)
    - S.T.I.R.: National Organizing Committee, AFL-CIO, Washington, DC, 1984-1985 (Box 183, Folder 19)
    - Where is the CIO going? By George Morris: New Century Publishers, 1949; cuid10684 (Box 142, Folder 48)
    - New England Labor News & Commentary: New England Labor News & Commentary, Inc., Nashua, NH, 1989; cuid10685 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - New Hampshire Labor News: New Hampshire Federation of Labor, Manchester, NH, 1952; cuid10686 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - IUC Action: New Jersey Industrial Union Council, AFL-CIO, Moorestown, NJ, 1996; cuid10687 (Box 142, Folder 49)
    - New Watch-Dog Committee: New Watch-dog Committee, Brooklyn, NY, 1975; cuid10688 (Box 142, Folder 50)
    - Industrial Relations: New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry, New York, NY, 1978 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Annual Dinner Dance and Awards Ceremony: New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1999; cuid10689 (Box 142, Folder 51)
    - Labor Chronicle: New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1958-1984; cuid10690 (Box 160, Folder 5-7, Box 210, Folder 7, Folder 13, Box 213, Folder 3, Folder 18, Box 221, Folder 11)
    - Labor Council Alert: New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1993; cuid10691 (Box 142, Folder 52)
    - Trade Union Handbook: New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1975, 1988; cuid10692 (Box 142, Folder 53, Box 198, Folder 21)
    - HSPAC News: New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO) - Human Service Providers Advisory Committee, New York, NY, 1990; cuid10693 (Box 142, Folder 54)
    - CIO Community Services Newsletter: New York City CIO Council - Community Services Committee, New York, NY, 1954; cuid10694 (Box 142, Folder 55)
    - Fellow Worker: New York District Council (Industrial Workers of the World), New York, NY, 1920; cuid10695 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Disadvantaged Teacher: New York Labor Committee, New York, NY, 1970; cuid10696 (Box 142, Folder 56)
    - The Preamble of the Industrial Workers of the World: New York Labor News Company, New York, NY, 1915; cuid10697 (Box 142, Folder 57)
    - Socialist Labor Party: New York Labor News Company, New York, NY, 1890-1930 (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - New York Labor Party: New York Labor Party, New York, NY, 1997-1998; cuid10698 (Box 142, Folder 58)
    - Labor Party Metro Active: New York Metro Chapter of the Labor Party, New York, NY, 1997-1998; cuid10699 (Box 142, Folder 59)
    - New York Credit Union News: New York State Credit Union League, Inc, New York, NY, 1936; cuid10700 (Box 142, Folder 60)
    - Combined Annual Reports of Officers of the New York State Federation of Labor: New York State Federation of Labor, Rochester, NY, 1946; cuid10701 (Box 172, Folder 28)
    - New York State Federation of Labor Bulletin: New York State Federation of Labor, New York, NY, 1936-1937; cuid10702 (Box 142, Folder 61)
    - Index: New York Trust Company, New York, NY, 1945; cuid10703 (Box 142, Folder 62)
    - League Bulletin: New York Women's Trade Union, New York, NY, 1940; cuid10704 (Box 142, Folder 63)
    - Strike Bulletin: Newspaper Guild of New York - World-Telegram & Sun Unit, New York, NY, 1950; cuid10705 (Box 142, Folder 64)
    - NMASS Bulletin = Boletin de NMASS: NMASS, New York, NY, 2003 (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - What is the non-partisan labor defense: Non-Partisan Labor Defense, New York, NY, circa 1940s; cuid10706 (Box 142, Folder 65)
    - Labor Report: North East Central Labor Council, AFL-CIO, Plattsburgh, NY, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Labor & Environment News: NYC Labor & Environment Network, New York, NY, 1995; cuid10707 (Box 142, Folder 66)
    - Wildcat Report: NY-NJ Wildcat Action Group, New York, NY, 1969-1970; cuid10708 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Labor Report: NYS Assembly Labor Committee, 1977; cuid10709 (Box 142, Folder 67)
    - Employee Bulletin: NYS Department of Labor, Albany, NY, 1982; cuid10710 (Box 142, Folder 68)
    - O4O Newsletter: October 4th Organization, Philadelphia, PA, 1973-1974; cuid10711 (Box 142, Folder 69, Box 180, Folder 1)
    - A Single Spark: October 4th Organization, Philadelphia, PA, 1973-1974; cuid10712 (Box 153, Folder 7, Box 210, Folder 10)
    - Call/El Clarin: October League, 1979; cuid10713 (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Owners at Work: Ohio Employee Ownership Center, Kent, OH, 2001; cuid10714 (Box 142, Folder 70)
    - Champ, Jr.: Ohio Valley District Council No. 2, Portsmouth, OH, 1950; cuid10715 (Box 142, Folder 71)
    - CIO News: Oil Workers International Union, Chicago, IL, 1944, 1946, 1950-1951; cuid10716 (Box 153, Folder 9, Box 159, Folder 5)
    - News from OCAW: Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (AFL-CIO), Denver, CO, 1989; cuid10717 (Box 142, Folder 72)
    - Handbook for OCAW Women: Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers, Denver, CO, 1973; cuid10718 (Box 142, Folder 73)
    - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Union News: Official Publication of Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers Intl. Union--CIO: Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Denver, CO, 1983-1984; cuid10719 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7069)
    - One Sky Report: One Sky Report, Saskatoon, Saskatchewan, 1981-1982 (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Constitution: Orange County Central Labor Council, Santa Ana, CA, Undated (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Oregon Labor Press: Oregon Labor Press, Portland, OR, 1981 (Box 213, Folder 20)
    - Build a National Workers Organizations; Stand Up Fight Together: Organizing Committee for a National Workers Organization, Milwaukee, WI, 1977; cuid10720 (Box 142, Folder 74)
    - Organizer: Organizing Committee for a National Workers Organization, Milwaukee, WI, 1977 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - Organizer: National Newsletter of the Organizing Committee for a National Workers Organization: Organizing Committee for a National Workers Organization, Milwaukee, WI, 1977-1978; cuid10721 (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Our Times: Our Times Cooperative, Toronto, Canada, 1982; cuid10722 (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Outlaw: Outlaw Collective, St. Louis, Mo., 1971; cuid10723 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - PACEsetter: PACE International Union, Nashville, TN, 1999-2000; cuid10724 (Box 153, Folder 13-14)
    - New York Workers' News and Perspective: Pasternack, A., Brooklyn, NY, 1976-1978; cuid10725 (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - Synopsis Report of the Fifty-Fifth Annual Convention of the Pennsylvania Federation of Labor: Pennsylvania Federation of Labor, Pittsburgh, PA, 1957 (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Bulletin of the People's Council of America: People's Council of America, New York, NY, 1917; cuid10726 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - People's Voice: People's Voice, Detroit, MI, 1974-1975; cuid10727 (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - People's Voice: People's Voice, Maywood, IL, 1973; cuid10728 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - People's Voice: People's Voice, Inc., Somerville, MA, 1973-1977; cuid10729 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Philadelphia Free Press: Philadelphia Free Press, Philadelphia, PA, 1973; cuid10730 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Trade Union Question: Philadelphia Organizing Committee, Philadelphia, PA, 1977; cuid10731 (Box 142, Folder 75)
    - Workers' Councils and the Economics of a Self-Managed Society: Philadelphia Solidarity, Philadelphia, PA, 1974; cuid10732 (Box 142, Folder 76)
    - Organizer: Philadelphia Workers' Organizing Committee, Philadelphia, Pa, 1975-1981, 1987-1988; cuid10733 (Box 148, Folder 1-5)
    - Turn It Around!: Philadelphia Workers' Organizing Committee, Philadelphia, Pa, 1971; cuid10734 (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Philly Facts: Philadelphia-TWU Local 235, Philadelphia, Pa, 1945; cuid10735 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Report of President Philip Murray to the Eighth Constitutional Convention of the CIO: Philip Murray/CIO, Atlantic City, NJ, 1946 (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - Work Ethics: Newsletter of the Plant Closures Project: Plant Closures Project, Oakland, CA, 1984; cuid10736 (Box 142, Folder 77)
    - Sargent Bulletin # 89: Porter Sargent, Boston, MA, 1940; cuid10737 (Box 142, Folder 78)
    - Progressive Voice: Progressive Group in Workers Alliance, New York, NY, 1938; cuid10738 (Box 142, Folder 79)
    - Pueblo: Pueblo, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1970; cuid10739 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Rank and Filer: Rank & Filer, New York, NY, 1970; cuid10740 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - New York Painter and Decorator: Rank and File Inter-Club Conference, New York, NY, 1936-1937; cuid10741 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Working for a Living: Rational Island Publishers, Seattle, WA, 1977; cuid10742 (Box 142, Folder 80)
    - TWU Free Press: Reick Committee in the Interest of Local 235, 1960; cuid10743 (Box 142, Folder 81)
    - Labor's Champion: Organ of the Central Committee of the Revolutionary Political Organization (Marxist-Leninist) USA: Revolutionary Political Organization, New Orleans, La, 1985-1991; cuid10744 (Box 147, Folder 1-6)
    - Call/El Clarín: Revolutionary Press, USA, 1978 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Workers' History Calendar: Revolutionary Union, Chicago, IL, 1973-1975; cuid10745 (Box 142, Folder 82)
    - Movin' On = Moviéndo se: Revolutionary Workers Congress, Detroit, MI, 1975; cuid10746 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Labor Challenge: Revolutionary Workers Party, Toronto, Canada, 1946, 1951-1952; cuid10747 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Worker: Rhode Island Workers Association, Providence, RI, 1975; cuid10748 (Box 142, Folder 83)
    - R.I.W.A. Organizing Center Reports/Assorted reports: Rhode Island Workers Association Organizing Center, Providence, RI, 1976; cuid10749 (Box 142, Folder 84)
    - People Get Ready: Richmond Worker's Committee, Richmond, CA, 1970; cuid10750 (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Row 'A' Review: Row 'A' Review Campaign Committee, 1944; cuid10751 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Local 6 Liberator: Save The Union Committee, New York, NY, 1951; cuid10752 (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Seattle Semi: Seattle Semi, Seattle, WA, 1976; cuid10753 (Box 142, Folder 85)
    - Sembrador: Sembrador, Fresno, CA, 1977 (Box 213, Folder 23)
    - Industrial & Allied Update: Service Employees International Union (SEIU) - Industrial & Allied Division (AFL-CIO, CLC), Washington, DC, 1988-1992; cuid10754 (Box 142, Folder 86)
    - Special Bulletin: Service Employees International Union, Local 32-J, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 185, Folder 13)
    - Meatballs: SHAP-affiliated, 2002; cuid10755 (Box 142, Folder 87)
    - Meatballs: SHAP Union, 2002 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Solidarity Organizing Committee/Comite Organizador Solidaridad: Solidarity Organizing Committee, Brooklyn, NY, 1992-1994; cuid10756 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Union Labor News: South Central Federation of Labor, Madison, WI, 1993; cuid10757 (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Southern Tenant Farmers' Union: Southern Tenant Farmers' Union, Memphis, TN, 1937 (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Third Annual Convention of the Southern Tenant Farmers' Union: Southern Tenant Farmers' Union, Muskogee, OK, 1937 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Fair Measure: Newsletter of Southerners for Economic Justice: Southerners for Economic Justice, Greenville, SC, 1978, 1982-1984; cuid10758 (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - The Spark: Spark, Detroit, MI, 1989; cuid10759 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Spark Western Voice for Revolution = Chispa de Revolution: SPARK-CHISPA, San Francisco, CA, 1966; cuid10760 (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - Speaking Out: Speaking Out, Detroit, MI, 1982; cuid10761 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Illinois Tradesman: Springfield Federation of Labor, Springfield, IL, 1954; cuid10762 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Minnesota Union Advocate: St. Paul Trades & Labor Assembly, St. Paul, MN, 1997; cuid10763 (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - Union Advocate: St. Paul Trades & Labor Assembly, St. Paul, MN, 1997; cuid10764 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Strike!: STRIKE! Publishing Association, 1981-1986; cuid10765 (Box 155, Folder 1-2)
    - Open City: Strike-New York, Bronx, NY, 1970; cuid10766 (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - Brockwood Review: Students and Faculty of Brockwood, Katonah, NY, 1929; cuid10767 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Union Voice: Suffolk County Head Start Union Workers, Amityville, NY, 1987; cuid10768 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - People Get Ready: Sunbeam Workers, Chicago, IL, circa 1970s; cuid10769 (Box 172, Folder 29)
    - El Obrero rebelde: Synthesis Publications, San Francisco, CA, 1979; cuid10770 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - 1954 Co-op Yearbook: The Cooperative League of the USA, Chicago, IL (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Florida Labor Advocate: The Florida Labor Advocate, Tampa, FL, 1954 (Box 221, Folder 14)
    - Blade and Stone: The Order of the Blade and the Whet-Stone, Miami, FL, 1995 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Outlaw Times: The Outlaw, Dallas, TX, 1971; cuid10771 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Peoples' Alliance Bulletin: The People's Alliance, New York, NY, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 16)
    - Red Album: Toiler, Cleveland, OH, 1921; cuid10772 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Toledo Consumers' League: Toledo Consumers' League, Toledo, OH, 1930, 1933; cuid10773 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Working Press: Tompkins/Cortland Labor Coalition (TCLC), Ithaca, NY, 1987-1994; cuid10774 (Box 155, Folder 6-7)
    - Discussion Bulletin: Trade Union Commission, 1976; cuid10775 (Box 172, Folder 22)
    - Rank and File Federationist/A.F. of L. Rank and File Federationist: Trade Union Committee for Unemployment Insurance Relief - A.F. of L. Trade Union Committee, New York, NY, 1933-1935; cuid10776 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - New York Teamster: Trade Union Courier, New York, NY, 1976; cuid10777 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Trade Union Courier: Trade Union Courier, New York, NY, 1948, 1978, 1997-2003; cuid10778 (Box 156, Folder 19-20, Box 157, Folder 1-3, Box 158, Folder 1-4, Box 210, Folder 8, Box 211, Folder 7-9, Box 212, Folder 1-2)
    - Union Courier: Trade Union Courier Publishing Corp., New York, NY, 1950; cuid10779 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Labor Herald Library: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, circa 1920s; cuid10780 (Box 143, Folder 7-8)
    - Third World Congress of the Red International of Labor Unions: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, 1924 (Box 198, Folder 19)
    - Vanguard: Trade Union Leadership Council, Inc., Detroit, MI, 1963; cuid10781 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Labor Party News: Trade Union Sponsoring Committee for a Labor Party Conference, New York, NY, 1936 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Demands for Unemployment Insurance Made upon the United States Congress: Trade Union Unity League, 1931; cuid10782 (Box 172, Folder 26)
    - Red International of Labour Unions: Trade Union Unity League of America, New York, NY, circa 1930; cuid10783 (Box 143, Folder 9)